import {Question} from '../helper/question';
import {QuestionType} from '../helper/QuestionType';
/**
 * Created by barthclem on 11/16/17.
 */
export const PseudoQuestions: Question [] =
    [
        {
            id: 1,
            category: 'General',
            type: QuestionType.TEXT,
            questionText: 'Who is Enitan?',
            options: ['Oba of Benin', 'A white man', 'Prince of Wales', 'I don\'t know'],
            answer: 'Prince of Wales'
        },
        {
            id: 2,
            category: 'General',
            type: QuestionType.TEXT,
            questionText: 'Where is OAU located?',
            options: ['Ife', 'Ile-Ife', 'Ilesa', 'Ile-Esa'],
            answer: 'Ile-Ife'
        },
        {
            id: 3,
            category: 'General',
            type: QuestionType.TEXT,
            questionText: 'Define Black',
            options: ['Black is dark', 'Black is beauty', 'I am black', 'Black is pride'],
            answer: 'Black is beauty'
        },
        {
            id: 4,
            category: 'General',
            type: QuestionType.TEXT,
            questionText: 'Who is General Pype',
            options: ['Pipe Lord', 'Pipe Gangmaster', 'Musician', 'A random guy'],
            answer: 'A random guy'
        },
        {
            id: 5,
            category: 'General',
            type: QuestionType.TEXT,
            questionText: 'What is unique',
            options: ['Personality', 'World View', 'Belief', 'Thought'],
            answer: 'Personality'
        },
        {
            id: 6,
            category: 'General',
            type: QuestionType.TEXT,
            questionText: 'Who is the President of Saudi Arabia',
            options: ['Bherdua Raheem', 'Lord Luggard', 'Question is wrong', 'You want war?'],
            answer: 'You want war?'
        },
        {
            id: 7,
            category: 'General',
            type: QuestionType.TEXT,
            questionText: 'Where is the most popular place in Africa',
            options: ['Lagos', 'Kano', 'Liberia', 'Accra'],
            answer: 'Lagos'
        },
        {
            id: 8,
            category: 'General',
            type: QuestionType.TEXT,
            questionText: 'What do you think about this App ?',
            options: ['Good', 'Just there', 'Awesome App', 'Very Good'],
            answer: 'Just there'
        },
        {
            id: 1,
            category: 'Social',
            type: QuestionType.TEXT,
            questionText: 'Which is most popular',
            options: ['Facebook', 'Instagram', 'Whatsapp', 'Twitter'],
            answer: 'Facebook'
        },
        {
            id: 2,
            category: 'Social',
            type: QuestionType.TEXT,
            questionText: 'Which is most useful',
            options: ['Facebook', 'Instagram', 'Whatsapp', 'Twitter'],
            answer: 'Twitter'
        },
        {
            id: 3,
            category: 'Social',
            type: QuestionType.TEXT,
            questionText: 'Which is used for sharing only pictures',
            options: ['Flickr', 'Instagram', 'Whatsapp', 'Twitter'],
            answer: 'Flickr'
        },
        {
            id: 4,
            category: 'Social',
            type: QuestionType.TEXT,
            questionText: 'Which one started first',
            options: ['Flickr', 'Instagram', 'Yahoo', 'Twitter'],
            answer: 'Yahoo'
        },
        {
            id: 5,
            category: 'Social',
            type: QuestionType.TEXT,
            questionText: 'Which is most abused',
            options: ['Facebook', 'Instagram', 'Whatsapp', 'Twitter'],
            answer: 'Facebook'
        },
        {
            id: 6,
            category: 'Social',
            type: QuestionType.TEXT,
            questionText: 'Which one is Donald Trump favorite',
            options: ['Facebook', 'Instagram', 'Whatsapp', 'Twitter'],
            answer: 'Twitter'
        },
        {
            id: 7,
            category: 'Social',
            type: QuestionType.TEXT,
            questionText: 'Which one is dead ?',
            options: ['2go', 'Badoo', 'Yahoo', 'Youtube'],
            answer: '2go'
        },
        {
            id: 8,
            category: 'Social',
            type: QuestionType.TEXT,
            questionText: 'Who is most popular ',
            options: ['Wizkid', 'Olamide', 'Davido', 'Duncan Mighty'],
            answer: 'Wizkid'
        },
        {
            id: 1,
            category: 'Religious',
            type: QuestionType.TEXT,
            questionText: 'Sola Scriptura is heretic',
            options: ['true', 'false', 'depends on definition of heresy', 'true but not entirely'],
            answer: 'depends on definition of heresy'
        },
        {
            id: 2,
            category: 'Religious',
            type: QuestionType.TEXT,
            questionText: 'There would be peace in the world without religion',
            options: ['true', 'false'],
            answer: 'false'
        },
        {
            id: 3,
            category: 'Religious',
            type: QuestionType.TEXT,
            questionText: 'What is religion',
            options: ['it is an act', 'the practice of belief in supreme being', 'most confusing discuss',
                'different narratives of thought'],
            answer: 'the practice of belief in supreme being'
        },
        {
            id: 4,
            category: 'Religious',
            type: QuestionType.TEXT,
            questionText: 'Rome predominantly practices',
            options: ['Christianity', 'Roman Catholicism', 'Orthodox Christianity', 'Pentecostalism'],
            answer: 'Roman Catholicism'
        },
        {
            id: 5,
            category: 'Religious',
            type: QuestionType.TEXT,
            questionText: 'The most popular religion in Iran is ?',
            options: ['Islam', 'Christianity', 'Ifa', 'Judaism'],
            answer: 'Islam'
        },
        {
            id: 6,
            category: 'Religious',
            type: QuestionType.TEXT,
            questionText: 'Who is an atheist',
            options: ['One that does not believe in God', 'One that does not believe the existence of God', 'nobody', 'somebody'],
            answer: 'One that does not believe the existence of God'
        },
        {
            id: 7,
            category: 'Religious',
            type: QuestionType.TEXT,
            questionText: 'What is the most popular religion?',
            options: ['Hinduism', 'Islam', 'Christianity', 'Ifa'],
            answer: 'Christianity'
        },
        {
            id: 8,
            category: 'Religious',
            type: QuestionType.TEXT,
            questionText: 'Define bible',
            options: ['Christian book', 'Living Word of God', 'Word of God', 'Recorded History'],
            answer: 'Living Word of God'
        },
        {
            id: 1,
            category: 'Education',
            type: QuestionType.TEXT,
            questionText: 'Define time',
            options: ['time is space', 'space is time', 'time is time', 'time is continous'],
            answer: 'time is time'
        },
        {
            id: 2,
            category: 'Education',
            type: QuestionType.TEXT,
            questionText: 'Define nursery',
            options: ['nursery is small', 'nursery is for kids', 'nursery is a stage', 'nursery on farm ?'],
            answer: 'nursery on farm'
        },
        {
            id: 3,
            category: 'Education',
            type: QuestionType.TEXT,
            questionText: 'Define date',
            options: ['date is time', 'date is days', 'date is day record', 'I don\'t know'],
            answer: 'I don\'t know'
        },
        {
            id: 4,
            category: 'Education',
            type: QuestionType.TEXT,
            questionText: 'Define emergency',
            options: ['Emergency is a state', 'Emergency is an act', 'Emergency is not real', 'empty'],
            answer: 'empty'
        },
    ];


export const QuestionData: Question [] =
    [
        {
            questionText: '_____ is the earliest form of computer?',
            answer: 'Abacus',
            options: [
                'Abacus',
                'Suan Pan',
                'Soroban',
                'Vedic Math'
            ],
            category: 'ICT',
            type: QuestionType.TEXT,
            id: 1
        },
        {
            questionText: 'Computers are classified into ____ generations',
            answer: '5',
            options: [
                '3',
                '2',
                '5',
                '4'
            ],
            category: 'ICT',
            type: QuestionType.TEXT,
            id: 2
        },
        {
            questionText: 'Calculate the volume of a cylinder of height 14cm and radius 3cm',
            answer: '396 cm cube',
            options: [
                '396 cm cube',
                '264 cm cube',
                '198 cm cube',
                '172 cm cube'
            ],
            category: 'ICT',
            type: QuestionType.TEXT,
            id: 3
        },
        {
            questionText: 'The following but one are examples of high level programming languages ',
            answer: 'Byte Code',
            options: [
                'Java',
                'Swift',
                'PHP',
                'Byte Code'
            ],
            category: 'ICT',
            type: QuestionType.TEXT,
            id: 4
        },
        {
            questionText: 'What was the weight of the ENIAC (Electronic Numerical Integrator and Computer)',
            answer: '30tonnes',
            options: [
                '30tonnes',
                '50tonnes',
                '90tonnes',
                '70tonnes'
            ],
            category: 'ICT',
            type: QuestionType.TEXT,
            id: 5
        },
        {
            questionText: 'Which of the generation computers was vacuum tube based',
            answer: 'First',
            options: [
                'First',
                'Second',
                'Third ',
                'Fourth'
            ],
            category: 'ICT',
            type: QuestionType.TEXT,
            id: 6
        },
        {
            questionText: 'What year was the second generation of computer invented',
            answer: '1957',
            options: [
                '1957',
                '1967',
                '1947',
                '1937'
            ],
            category: 'ICT',
            type: QuestionType.TEXT,
            id: 7
        },
        {
            questionText: 'What is the full meaning of IBM?',
            answer: 'International Business Machines',
            options: [
                'Incorporated Business Methods',
                'International Business Machines',
                'International Bus Media',
                'International Bayes Machines'
            ],
            category: 'ICT',
            type: QuestionType.TEXT,
            id: 8
        },
        {
            questionText: 'Who designed the Analytical Engine called Abacus Computer',
            answer: 'Charles Babbage',
            options: [
                'Charles Newton',
                'Charles Macintosh',
                'Charles Babbage',
                'Charles Charlton'
            ],
            category: 'ICT',
            type: QuestionType.TEXT,
            id: 9
        },
        {
            questionText: 'What is another name for Network Card?',
            answer: 'Network Interface Card',
            options: [
                'Neural Intelligence Card',
                'Naturally Inactive Card',
                'Native Indoor Card',
                'Network Interface Card'
            ],
            category: 'ICT',
            type: QuestionType.TEXT,
            id: 10
        },
        {
            questionText: 'I questionTextways preferred unripe plaintain ......... yam. Which of these best completes the sentence? ',
            answer: 'to',
            options: [
                'to',
                'than',
                'from',
                'for'
            ],
            category: 'English',
            type: QuestionType.TEXT,
            id: 1
        },
        {
            questionText: 'She hasn\'t come home.......',
            answer: 'Yet',
            options: [
                'Still',
                'Till',
                'Yet',
                'Already'
            ],
            category: 'English',
            type: QuestionType.TEXT,
            id: 2
        },
        {
            questionText: 'The new teacher urged the lazy students to turn a new leaf. This means that the teacher urged the students to',
            answer: 'improve their behaviour',
            options: [
                'improve their behaviour',
                'turn to the next page of their book',
                'stir the leave in thr composit pit',
                'strike a balance between play and hardwork'
            ],
            category: 'English',
            type: QuestionType.TEXT,
            id: 3
        },
        {
            questionText: 'But for the timely ......., Of the police, there would have been a riot',
            answer: 'intervention',
            options: [
                'interference',
                'intrusion',
                'intervention',
                'interruption'
            ],
            category: 'English',
            type: QuestionType.TEXT,
            id: 4
        },
        {
            questionText: '(Words and Opposite) The children expected to be praised for putting out the fire, but they were........ For taking such a risk',
            answer: 'rebuked',
            options: [
                'rebuked',
                'accused',
                'despised',
                'sentenced'
            ],
            category: 'English',
            type: QuestionType.TEXT,
            id: 5
        },
        {
            questionText: '(best completes) The man asked ...........',
            answer: 'who I was',
            options: [
                'who am i',
                'that who are you',
                'who I am',
                'who I was'
            ],
            category: 'English',
            type: QuestionType.TEXT,
            id: 6
        },
        {
            questionText: '(nearest in meaning). The foreman believed that with the augemented workforce, the construction job would take one monrth to complete',
            answer: 'enlarged',
            options: [
                'skilled',
                'enlarged',
                'hired',
                'determined'
            ],
            category: 'English',
            type: QuestionType.TEXT,
            id: 7
        },
        {
            questionText: 'The man advised his children not to give ..... to the temptations of the city.',
            answer: 'in',
            options: [
                'off',
                'up',
                'in',
                'on'
            ],
            category: 'English',
            type: QuestionType.TEXT,
            id: 8
        },
        {
            questionText: '(nearest in meaning) The children were warned not to be unduly inquisitive',
            answer: 'curious',
            options: [
                'naughty',
                'playful',
                'troublesome',
                'curious'
            ],
            category: 'English',
            type: QuestionType.TEXT,
            id: 9
        },
        {
            questionText: '(Most Approriate) When it came to the question of an increase in allowances, the striking workers spoke with one voice. This means',
            answer: 'were unanimous in their position',
            options: [
                'became frightened',
                'appointed one of them as their spokesman',
                'repeated their demand in a chorus',
                'were unanimous in their position'
            ],
            category: 'English',
            type: QuestionType.TEXT,
            id: 10
        },
        {
            questionText: 'When was the last  National Population Census Held',
            answer: '2006',
            options: [
                '2006',
                '2012',
                '2003',
                '2001'
            ],
            category: 'Current Affairs',
            type: QuestionType.TEXT,
            id: 1
        },
        {
            questionText: 'Who is the Deputy Governor of Oyo State',
            answer: 'Chief Moses Alake Adeyemo',
            options: [
                'Chief Moses Alake Adeyemo',
                'Chief Matthew Adeleke ',
                'Chief Murphy Akinwale',
                'Chief Mark Akiode'
            ],
            category: 'Current Affairs',
            type: QuestionType.TEXT,
            id: 2
        },
        {
            questionText: 'When was the first military coup?',
            answer: '1966',
            options: [
                '1956',
                '1960',
                '1963',
                '1966'
            ],
            category: 'Current Affairs',
            type: QuestionType.TEXT,
            id: 3
        },
        {
            questionText: 'Who is the immediate past Governor of Oyo State',
            answer: 'Christopher Alao-Akala',
            options: [
                'Abiola Ajimobi',
                'Christopher Alao-Akala',
                'Dr Lam Adesina',
                'Rashidi Adewolu Ladoja'
            ],
            category: 'Current Affairs',
            type: QuestionType.TEXT,
            id: 4
        },
        {
            questionText: 'Who is the Richest man in Africa',
            answer: 'Aliko Dangote',
            options: [
                'Aliko Dangote',
                'Micheal Adenuga',
                'Christoffel Wiese',
                'Naguib Sawiris'
            ],
            category: 'Current Affairs',
            type: QuestionType.TEXT,
            id: 5
        },
        {
            questionText: 'The name of the minister of communication in Nigeria is',
            answer: 'Prof Lai Mohammad',
            options: [
                'Prof Lai Mohammad',
                'Abdur-Raheem Adebayo Shittu ',
                'Senator Ben Murray Bruce',
                'Babtunde Raji Fashola'
            ],
            category: 'Current Affairs',
            type: QuestionType.TEXT,
            id: 6
        },
        {
            questionText: 'Schools are for ministry if education as MTN is for ____ ministry',
            answer: 'Communication',
            options: [
                'Labour',
                'Agriculture',
                'Communication',
                'Sports'
            ],
            category: 'Current Affairs',
            type: QuestionType.TEXT,
            id: 7
        },
        {
            questionText: 'Who is the current Nigerian Deputy Senate president?',
            answer: 'Senator Ike Ekweremadu',
            options: [
                'Senator Ben Bruce',
                'Senator Bukola Saraki',
                'Senator Ike Ekweremadu',
                'Senator Abiola Ajimobi'
            ],
            category: 'Current Affairs',
            type: QuestionType.TEXT,
            id: 8
        },
        {
            questionText: 'Who was the first woman to drive a car in Nigeria?',
            answer: 'Funmilayo Ransom Kuti',
            options: [
                'Funmilola Kuti',
                'Funmilayo Ransom Kuti',
                'Iyalode Tinubu',
                'Chimamanda Ngozi '
            ],
            category: 'Current Affairs',
            type: QuestionType.TEXT,
            id: 9
        },
        {
            questionText: 'What does the white color in Nigeria flag stands for?',
            answer: 'Peace',
            options: [
                'Joy',
                'Protest',
                'Strike',
                'Peace'
            ],
            category: 'Current Affairs',
            type: QuestionType.TEXT,
            id: 10
        },
        {
            questionText: '______ for 4 to the 4th power?',
            answer: '256',
            options: [
                '16',
                '64',
                '256',
                '512'
            ],
            category: 'Maths',
            type: QuestionType.TEXT,
            id: 1
        },
        {
            questionText: 'When asked how old she was, Beth replied “In two years I will be twice as old as I was five years ago”. How old is she?',
            answer: '12',
            options: [
                '8',
                '10',
                '12',
                '14'
            ],
            category: 'Maths',
            type: QuestionType.TEXT,
            id: 2
        },
        {
            questionText: 'Which weighs more? A pound of iron or a pound of copper?',
            answer: 'Both weigh the same',
            options: [
                'Iron',
                'Copper',
                'They can\'t be compared',
                'Both weigh the same'
            ],
            category: 'Maths',
            type: QuestionType.TEXT,
            id: 3
        },
        {
            questionText: 'Divide 40 by half and add ten. What is the answer?',
            answer: '90',
            options: [
                '80',
                '90',
                '100',
                '110'
            ],
            category: 'Maths',
            type: QuestionType.TEXT,
            id: 4
        },
        {
            questionText: 'A farmer has 15 cows, all but 8 die. How many does he have left?',
            answer: '8',
            options: [
                '8',
                '6',
                '4',
                '7'
            ],
            category: 'Maths',
            type: QuestionType.TEXT,
            id: 5
        },
        {
            questionText: ' If the difference of two numbers is 8 and their product is 16, what is the sum of their squares?',
            answer: '96',
            options: [
                '100',
                '98',
                '96',
                '94'
            ],
            category: 'Maths',
            type: QuestionType.TEXT,
            id: 6
        },
        {
            questionText: '1, 5, 10, 16, 23, x. What is x?',
            answer: '31',
            options: [
                '11',
                '21',
                '31',
                '41'
            ],
            category: 'Maths',
            type: QuestionType.TEXT,
            id: 7
        },
        {
            questionText: '1, 11, 21, 1211, 111221,x. What is x?',
            answer: '312211',
            options: [
                '312211',
                '512211',
                '412211',
                '61211'
            ],
            category: 'Maths',
            type: QuestionType.TEXT,
            id: 8
        },
        {
            questionText: '1, 1,4,15,64,x. What is x',
            answer: '360',
            options: [
                '180',
                '360',
                '540',
                '720'
            ],
            category: 'Maths',
            type: QuestionType.TEXT,
            id: 9
        },
        {
            questionText: 'Paul needs 13 bottles of lemonade from the shop but he can only carry 3 bottles at a time. How many trips to the shop will Paul need to make?',
            answer: '5',
            options: [
                '10',
                '5',
                '20',
                '15'
            ],
            category: 'Maths',
            type: QuestionType.TEXT,
            id: 10
        }
    ];
